 module.exports.dataQuestion = {
   d: [
     {
       id: 1,
       question: "Which is greater than 4?",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: 5 },
         { id2: 2, opt2: -5 },
         { id3: 3, opt3: -1 / 2 },
         { id4: 4, opt4: -25 },
       ],
       correctAns: 1,
     },
     {
       id: 2,
       question: "Which is the smallest?",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: -1 },
         { id2: 2, opt2: -1 / 2 },
         { id3: 3, opt3: 0 },
         { id4: 4, opt4: 3 },
       ],
       correctAns: 1,
     },
     {
       id: 3,
       question: "Combine terms: 12a + 26b -4b – 16a.",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: " 4a + 22b" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "-28a + 30b" },
         { id3: 3, opt3: "-4a + 22b," },
         { id4: 4, opt4: "28a + 30b" },
       ],
       correctAns: 3,
     },
     {
       id: 4,
       question: "(4 – 5) – (13 – 18 + 2).",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: -1 },
         { id2: 2, opt2: -2 },
         { id3: 3, opt3: 1 },
         { id4: 4, opt4: 2 },
       ],
       correctAns: 4,
     },
     {
       id: 5,
       question: "What is |-26|?",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: 26 },
         { id2: 2, opt2: -26 },
         { id3: 3, opt3: 0 },
         { id4: 4, opt4: 1 },
       ],
       correctAns: 2,
     },
     {
       id: 6,
       question: "Multiply: (x – 4)(x + 5)",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: " x2 + 5x - 20" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "x2 - 4x - 20," },
         { id3: 3, opt3: "x2 - x - 20," },
         { id4: 4, opt4: "x2 + x - 20" },
       ],
       correctAns: 4,
     },
     {
       id: 7,
       question: " Factor: 5x2 – 15x – 20.",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: "5(x-4)(x+1)" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "-2(x-4)(x+5)" },
         { id3: 3, opt3: " -5(x+4)(x-1)," },
         { id4: 4, opt4: "5(x+4)(x+1)." },
       ],
       correctAns: 1,
     },
     {
       id: 8,
       question: "Factor: 3y(x – 3) -2(x – 3).",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: "(x – 3)(x – 3" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "(x – 3)2" },
         { id3: 3, opt3: " (x – 3)(3y – 2)" },
         { id4: 4, opt4: "3y(x – 3)." },
       ],
       correctAns: 3,
     },
     {
       id: 9,
       question: "Solve for x: 2x – y = (3/4)x + 6.",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: "(y + 6)/5" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "4(y + 6)/5" },
         { id3: 3, opt3: " (y + 6)" },
         { id4: 4, opt4: " 4(y - 6)/5." },
       ],
       correctAns: 2,
     },
     {
       id: 10,
       question: "Find the value of 3 + 2 • (8 – 3)",
       options: [
         { id1: 1, opt1: " 25" },
         { id2: 2, opt2: "13" },
         { id3: 3, opt3: " 17" },
         { id4: 4, opt4: " 24" },
       ],
       correctAns: 4,
     },
   ],
 };


